Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Irish Americana Collection AIA.031.004
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Sheet Music (Irish), 1817-1995
  - S
    - Sing Me An Irish Come-All-Ye, 1911 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Sing to Me of Ould Ireland, 1927 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Singer Was Irish, The, 1914 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Sister of Rosie O'Grady, The, 1918 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Skids Are Out To-Day, The, 1879 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Skin-A-Ma-Rink-A-Rink-A-Ree, 1924 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Slaunthe!, 1918 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Smiles and the Tears of Killarney, The, 1917 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Smiling Irish Eyes, 1929 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Snowy-Breasted Pearl, The, 1912 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - So Long, Mister Flanagan, 1910 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Soldier's Song, The, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Solid for Mulhooly, 1881 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Soliloquy, The, 1903 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Somewhere in France Dear Mother, 1915 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Somewhere in Ireland, 1917 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Songs in Exile, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Songs of Shamus O'Brien, 1866 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Songtime in Erin, 1923 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Son of an Irishman, The, 1913 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Song that Reaches Irish Hearts, The, 1911 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Squaw Colleen, 1910 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Steerin' for Erin, 1923 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - St. James Infirmary, 1930 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Stone Outside Dan Murphy's Door, The, 1895 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Story the Shamrock Told, The, 1913 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - St. Patrick's Day, undated (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - St. Patrick's Day (2), undated (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - St. Patrick's Day in the USA, 1918 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - St. Patrick's Day is a Bad Day for Coons, 1901 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - St. Patrick's Day Waltz, 1856 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Sullivan, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Sunday Night at Nellie's Home, 1894 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Supposin', 1909 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Sure Me Heart Is Longin' For You Dear Old Ireland, 1918 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Sweet Eileen Asthore, 1912 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Sweet Eileen Machree, 1891 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Sweet Irish Rose, 1915 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Sweet Irish Sweetheart of Mine, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Sweet Katie Kilcaire, 1874 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Sweet Katie, the Pride of Tralee, undated (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Sweet Katie Riley, 1895 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Sweet Katy Carney, My Lass from Killarney, 1898 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Sweet Little Irish Girl, 1910 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Sweet Little Irish Maiden, 1896 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Sweet Little Kate Maloney, 1900 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Sweet Little Kate McCoy, 1894 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Sweet Little Mollie O'Neal, 1897 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Sweet Little Peggy O'Shea, 1916 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Sweet Mary Ann, 1878 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Sweet Molly Malone, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Sweet Norah Daly, 1919 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Sweet Nora Doone, 1907 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Sweet Nora O'Neale, 1902 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Sweet Rosie O'Grady, nd, 1896, 1924, 1944 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Sweet Violets, 1882 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Sweetest Little Girl in Tipperary, The, 1928 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Sweetheart Darlin', 1933 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Sweetheart of O'Callahan's Mills, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Sweetheart Song, 1916 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Swim Out O'Grady, 1894 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - T
    - Taffy's Got His Jenny in Glamorgan, 1915 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Take a Look at Molly, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Take Me Back to Erin's Isle Once More, 1915 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Take Me Back to Ireland to My Little Irish Rose, 1913 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Take Me Back to My Sweet Shannon Rose, 1918 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Take Off Your Hats to Old Ireland, 1910 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Tam O'Shanter, undated (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Teaching McFadden to Waltz, 1890 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Tears of an Irish Mother, The, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Tears of the Shannon, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Teddy O'Neil, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Tell It To Sweeny, 1910 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Tell the Band to Play an Irish Tune, 1906 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Terence's Farewell to Kathleen, undated (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Thady O'Flinn, undated (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - That Little Bit of Green, 1910 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - That Little Old House of O'Reilly's, 1922 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - That Old Irish Mother of Mine, 1920, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - That Tumble-Down Shack in Athlone, 1918 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - That's How I Spell I-R-E-L-A-N-D, 1931 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - That's How the Shannon Flows, 1915 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - That's How You Can Tell They're Irish, 1920 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - That's Irish Love, 1912 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - That's the Irish in Me, 1918 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - That's the Meaning of I-R-E-L-A-N-D, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - That's What Ireland Means to Me, 1917 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - That's What You Get for Being Irish, 1908 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - That's Why God Loves the Irish, 1919 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - There Goes McManus, 1889 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - There Never Was a Coward Where the Shamrock Grows, 1880 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - There'll Never Be a League of Nations Without Ireland, 1920 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - There's A Charm of Dear Old Ireland in Your Eyes, 1918 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - There's a Dear Spot in Ireland, 1878 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - There's a Dear Spot in Ireland (2), 1917 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - There's a Heart in Old Ireland, undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - There's a Little Bit of Irish Everywhere, 1919 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - There's a Little Bit of Irish in Sadie Cohn, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - There's A Little Bit of Irish in Us All, 1938 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - There's a Mother Back in Ireland Waits for Me, 1914 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - There's a Rose in Old Erin, 1915 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - There's a Rose that is Blooming in Ireland, 1917 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - There's a Typical Tipperary Over Here, 1920 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - There's a Wee Bit of Blarney in Killarney, 1915 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - There's Another Angel Now in Old Killarney, 1917 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Theres No Song Like an Irish Song, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - There's Nothing Like the Smile of the Irish, 1941 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - There's Something in the Name of Ireland, 1917 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - They Sail'd Away, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - They Were Irish, 1906 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - They've Won Every Nation's Battles But Their Own, 1910 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Tho' I Had a Bit o' the Devil in Me, She Had the Ways of an Angel, Had She, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Tho' I'm a Long Long Way from Tipperary, 1914 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Those Songs Mother Used to Sing, 1904 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Three Leaves of Shamrock, 1890 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Three Leaves of Shamrock (2), 1889 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Three Lovely Lasses in Bannion, 1940 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Throw Him Down, McCloskey, 1942 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Till Ireland's Wrongs Are Righted, 1880 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Till My Luck Comes Rolling Along, 1922 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Tim Rooney's at the Fightin'!, 1915 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Tipperary, 1907 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Tipperary (2), undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Tipperary Guards, 1915 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Tipperary March, 1908 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Tipperary Twirl, The, 1911 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Tip-Top Tipperary Mary, 1914 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Tis A Mem'ry of Your Daddy And That Isle Across the Sea, 1915 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Tis an Irish Girl I Love and She's Just Like You, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Tis Only A Sprig of Shamrock, 1915 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Tis the Last Rose of Summer, undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - To H-L Wid Reform, 1898 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Told You So, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Too-Ra-Loo-Ra-Loo-Ral That's An Irish Lullaby, 1913, 1941, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Top o' the Mornin', 1905 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Top o' the Mornin' (2), 1907 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Top o' the Mornin', The, 1920 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Top o' the Morning, The, 1909 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - To You it's Only Ireland, undated (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Twas Only an Irishman's Dream, 1916 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Two Irish Eyes, undated (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Two Irish Eyes of Tender Blue, 1900 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Two Laughing Irish Eyes, 1915 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Two More to Come, 1883 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - U
    - Umph-Ah-Ah, 1895 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Uncle Reilly, 1890 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Under the Irish Moon, 1909 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Up Comes McGinty, 1915 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - V
    - Vales of Killarney, The, undated (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Variations on an Irish Melody, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Vocal Gems, undated (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - W
    - Wait till I lay my hands upon McNally!, 1893 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - We Americans, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - We Couldn't Get Along Without the Irish, 1912 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Wearers of the Green, 1906 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Wearing of the Green, 1865 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Wearing of the Green, The, 1860 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Wearing of the Green, The (2), 1909 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Wedding of Barney and Bedalia, The, 1904 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - We'll Go Back to Erin Someday Mavourneen, 1909 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Well, the Irish and the Germans Got Together, 1928 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - What's the Matter with the Irish, 1916 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - When Chu-Ching-San Weds Paddy McCann, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - When Fortune Smiles on You, 1916 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - When Hogan Paid His Rent, 1933 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - When I Come Back to Erin, 1916 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - When I Dream of Killarney and You, 1915 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - When I Dream of Old Erin, 1912, 1931 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - When I Found You, 1917 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - When I Look In Your Eyes, Mavourneen, 1918 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - When I Met You at the Fair in Tipperary, 1912 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - When I Rode on the Choo Choo Cars, 1905 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - When Ireland Comes Into Her Own, 1919 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - When Ireland Takes Her Place Among the Nations of the Earth, 1919 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - When Irish Eyes Are Smiling, 1912 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - When Irish Toes Are Waltzing, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - When It's Moonlight in Mayo, 1913 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - When It's Moonlight in Mayo (2), 1954 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - When It's Springtime in Killarney, 1915, 1916 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - When John McCormack Sings A Song, 1915 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - When Johnny Comes Marching Home, 1863 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - When June Comes Along With A Song, 1923 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - When Kelly Sang Killarney, 1917 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - When My Girl From Tipp'rary Tips Me, 1907 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - When Old Ireland Is Forgotten, 1914 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - When Reuben Comes to Town, 1900 (Box 41, Folder 3A)
    - When Rubenstein and Mendelssohn Played the Wearing of the Green, 1912 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - When Scanlan Sang Mavourneen, 1917 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - When the Angelus is Ringing in Ireland, 1923 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - When the Bloom is on the Clover, Molly Dear, 1907 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - When the Dew is on the Clover in Kildare, 1909 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - When the Fightin' Irish Come Home, 1919 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - When the Gates of Heaven Opened, 1917 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - When the Moon Shines in Ireland, 1914, 1917 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - When the Rose of Tralee Met Danny Boy, 1940 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - When the Sun Sets in Galway, 1915 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - When the Sun Sets in Ireland, 1917 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - When the Sunbeams are Kissing the Roses, 1919 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - When They Planted the Shamrock, 1928 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - When They Play the River Shannon, 1916 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - When They Sing the Wearin' of the Green, 1929 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - When You and I Were Young, Maggie, nd, 1866, 1935 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - When You Break an Irishman's Heart, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - When You Come Back, 1928 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - When You Talk about Old Ireland, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Where Be Going?, 1898 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Where Irish Skies Are Smiling, 1918 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Where Is Mavourneen Tonight?, 1904 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Where the Golden Rod is Waving, Mollie Dear, 1906 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Where the River Liffy Flows, 1916 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Where the River Shannon Flows, 1905 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Where the Shamrock Grows, 1916 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Where the Shandon Bells Are Ringing, 1914 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Where the Shannon Flows Down to the Sea, 1938 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Where the Silvery Sleney's Flowing, 1912 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Where the Sparrows and Chippies Parade, 1888 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Where's Kitty O'Brien?, 1910 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - While the Irish Moon Rolls On, 1932 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Who Ever Heard of and Irishman Singing the Blues?, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Who Said the Irish Don't Love Liberty?, 1919 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Who Threw the Overalls in Mistress Murphy's Chowder?, 1932 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Why Did They Sell Killarney?, 1899 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Why Don't They Dance the Good Old Dances of Ireland, 1912 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Why Not Sing "Wearin' Of The Green", 1915 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Why Paddy's Always Poor, 1886 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Widow Machree, nd, 1916 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Widow Nolan's Goat, The, 1881 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Widow of a German Threw Him Down, The, 1918 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Wild Irish Boy, The, 1919 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Wild Irish Rose That God Gave Me, The, 1917 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Winging Your Way to Ireland, undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - With My Shillelagh Under My Arm, 1936 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - With the Last Rose of Summer, 1916 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Won't You Come Back to Mother Machree, 1923 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Won't You Come Back to Old Ireland, 1914 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Word From An Irishman's Tongue, The, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Would God I Were the Tender Apple Blossom, 1932 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Y
    - Yoo-La, 1909 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - You Are My Irish Lily, 1906 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - You Brought Ireland Right Over To Me, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - You Can Tell That I'm Irish, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - You Can't Deny You're Irish, 1918 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - You Can't Get Away From the Blarney, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - You Can't Win A War Without the Irish, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - You Don't Have to Be Irish to Be Welcome in an Irishman's Home, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - You Don't Have to Come from Ireland to Be Irish, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - You Remind Me of Dear Old Ireland, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - You Remind Me of My Mother, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - You Will Have to Sing an Irish Song, 1908 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - You'll Find a Little Bit of Ireland Everywhere, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - You'll Soon Forget Kathleen, undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Your Dear Old Dad Was Irish, 1914 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - You're Irish and You're Beautiful, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - You're the Sweetest Girl in Ireland, 1913 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - You're the Sweetest Rose Killarney Ever Grew, 1918 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - You're the Sweetest Rose that Grows in Old Killarney, 1913 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Yours Truly Mr. Dooley, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - You've Stolen the Key to My Heart, 1915 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Accretions
    - The Irish Jaunting Car, 1855 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Garret O'Magh, 1900 (Box 60, Folder 2, Box 62, Folder 46)
    - A Little Bit of Heave Shure They Call It Ireland, 1914 (Box 60, Folder 3, Box 62, Folder 44)
    - There Goes Muldoon the Solid Man (An Irish Character Song), undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Kerry Dance, 1941 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Irish Diamonds, undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - The Song That Reaches Irish Hearts, 1914 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Katie, 1906 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - God is Good to the Irish, 1927 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Ireland, Mother Ireland, 1922 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Kelly's Gone to Kingdom Come, 1910 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Overture of Irish Melodies, 1909 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Bring Back the Roses Kathleen Mavoureen, 1918 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - When the Sun Sets in Ireland, 1917 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Ireland, I'm For You, 1916 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Sweet Eileen Asthore, 1912 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Every Lane Must Have A Turn, 1907 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - That old Fashioned Mother of Mine, 1918 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - If You Ever Go to Ireland, 1944 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Edmund Burke, 1905 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - River Shannon Syncopated Waltz, 1912 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - My Sweet Little Colleen (From County Kildare), 1915 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Shandon Bell's Waltz, undated (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Back to Old Erin (Ballad), 1914 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - When You Look in the Heart of a Shamrock, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Irish Songs, 1907 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - There's A Typical Tipperary Over Here You'd Think That You Were Home In Ireland, undated (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - If I Knock the "L" Out of Kelly, 1916 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - My Bright Irish Girl, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Finnigan's Irish Band Irish March Song, 1908 (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - When Old Ireland is Forgotten, 1914 (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - There's Something in the Name of Ireland That the Whole World Seems to Love, 1917 (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Are You Mo-ri-ar-i-ty?, undated (Box 60, Folder 33)
    - Darling Nellie Gray, 1938 (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - Dream Girl O'Mine, undated (Box 60, Folder 35)
    - When Ireland Comes Into Her Own, 1919 (Box 60, Folder 36)
    - An Old Irish Melody - Would God I Were the Tender Apple Blossom, 1932 (Box 60, Folder 37)
    - Eileen (from Old Killarney), 1911, 1914 (Box 60, Folder 38, Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Erin's Isle and You, 1914 (Box 60, Folder 39)
    - I'll Take You Home Again, Kathleen, 1943 (Box 60, Folder 40)
    - I Love A Wee Bit of Irish, 1924 (Box 60, Folder 41)
    - New Great Song, 1904 (Box 60, Folder 42)
    - Irish Sketches, 1916 (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - Going My Way, 1944 (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Dainty Little Love, undated (Box 60, Folder 45)
    - All My Life, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 46)
    - I'm Looking Over A Four Leaf Clover, 1927 (Box 60, Folder 47)
    - There's A Four Leaf Clover in My Pocket (And a Horse -- Shoe Over My Door), 1929 (Box 60, Folder 48)
    - Mother in Ireland, 1922 (Box 60, Folder 49)
    - Too-Ra-Loo-Ra-Loo-Ral That's An Irish Lullaby, 1913 (Box 60, Folder 50)
    - Christmas in Killarney, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 51)
    - In the Shadow of the Dear Old Blarney Stone, 1912 (Box 60, Folder 52)
    - Eileen Allanna, undated (Box 60, Folder 53)
    - Patsy Dear, 1907 (Box 60, Folder 54)
    - Those Irish Eyes, 1929 (Box 60, Folder 55)
    - An Irish Girl, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 56)
    - Along the Rocky Road to Dublin, 1915 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Arrahwana, 1906 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - His Heart's Desire, 1916 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Bells of Killarney, 1913 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Barney Brallaghan, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - If It Wasn't for the Irish and the Jews, 1912 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Mother Machree, undated (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Molly O (I Love You), 1921 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Mavourneen, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - The Irish Tango, 1914 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Irish Ma O'Mine, undated (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - An Irish Love Song, 1895 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Martin Tucker, undated (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Trail on the Tail O' Me (Mush, Mush, Mush), 1945 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Chimmie Faden, 1896 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - You'll Find A Shamrock Down in the Garden Ev'ry Irish Heart, 1892 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Arrah-Na-Pogue, 1903 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Jack's Romance, 1914 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Yaka Hula Hickey Dula, 1916 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Barry of Ballymore (Chauncey Olcott), 1909 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Who Threw the Overalls in Mistress Murphy's Chowder?, 1937 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - When the River Shannon Flows, 1907 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Where Is My Mama?, 1914 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - When You Wore A Tulip and I Wore A Big Red Rose, 1914 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - When You're A Long, Long Way From Home, 1914 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - When You and I Were Young Maggie, undated (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - When The Irish Are On Parade, undated (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - When It's Moonlight in Mayo, undated (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Chauncey Olcott's Greatest Songs Successes, undated (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - The Lament of the Irish Emigrant, 1842 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Knights of the Mystic Star, 1891 (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Just A Girl That Men Forget (Ballad), undated (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Andrew Mack's New Songs, undated (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - I Wish I Knew, undated (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - I Want an Irish Rose, undated (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - I Want A Girl Just Like the Girl That Married Dear Old Dad, undated (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - It's Only a Step from Killarney to Heaven, undated (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - It's the Same of Shillelagh, undated (Box 61, Folder 38)
    - Those Songs My Mother Used to Sing, undated (Box 61, Folder 39)
    - When Irish Eyes Are Smiling, undated (Box 61, Folder 40)
    - Misc - Handwritten Sheet Music (Irish), undated (Box 61, Folder 41)
    - Gems from Glen-da-Lough, undated (Box 61, Folder 42)
    - If We Can't Be The Same Old Sweethearts We'll Just Be the Same Old Friends, 1915 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Honorah!, 1906 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Has Anybody Here Seen Kelly?, 1909 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - In Ireland, 1906 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Maoushla, 1911 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Give Me A Little Bit More Than You Gave Reilly, 1917 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Be My Tipperary Bride, 1912 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Blime Me, O'Reilly (You're Doing Quite Well), 1914 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Come Back to Erin, 1909 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Once Upon A Time, 1916 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Dear Mother Mine, 1915 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Eileen, 1917 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Hearts of Erin, 1917 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Fritz in Ireland, 1879 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Faugh-a-Ballagh (Fog-A-Bolla), 1917 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - I'm Proud I'm Irish, 1895 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Irish Songs, 1908 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Morton Downey's Collection of Irish Songs, 1943 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Says I to Myself, Says I, 1917 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - The Rosary, 1912 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Maggie Murphy's Home, 1890 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Phil the Fluter's Ball, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - A Perfect Day, 1910 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Paddy's Jig, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Paddy McGinty's Goat, 1917 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Over the Moutain, 1881 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - The Orange, the White, and the Green, 1919 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Oh the Irish Hearts, 1923 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Nearer My God, to Thee, 1907 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - A Night Cap, a Night Cap, 1880 (Box 62, Folder 31)